

# **MATTHEW HEFNER**

142 ALLENDALE CIRCLE, TROUTMAN, NC, 28166

# **AREAS OF EXPERTISE**

- Entry level programming and app development skills
- Project Management
- Strong Leadership role
- Excellent critical thinker and problem solver

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Competent Skills: Java, Kotlin, Python, HTML, CSS, Selenium, Appium, Photoshop Entry Skills: C, SQL, R, JavaScript

## **EDUCATION**

BS, COMPUTER SCIENCE WITH INFORMATION SYSTEMS MINOR • MAY 2019 • CATAWBA COLLEGE

- GPA: 3.99
- Junior Marshall
- Membership in: Alpha Chi, Kappa Mu Epsilon (Vice President)

## **PROFILE**

Creative programmer and developer with undergraduate experience in computer science and information technology. Well versed in algorithms, data structures, software development life cycle, and efficient coding practices. Experience and interests in Bluetooth Low Energy beacon technology and Android Development.

Portfolio can be found at https://matthefner.github.io./

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### QA TESTER • RETAIL BUSINESS SERVICES • JAN. 2019 - PRESENT

Responsible for creating, reviewing, and executing test cases and other testing artifacts using Selenium and Azure Pipelines. Used agile methodology in weekly sprints to produce results.

### INTERNSHIP • CATAWBA COLLEGE • OCT. 2018 - DEC. 2018

Involves the responsibilities of managing social media for the Center for the Environment as well as developing a new look for the current website with WordPress. Best practices for website design and social media are used throughout the duration of the internship.

#### INTERNSHIP • ST. JOHN'S LUTHERAN CHURCH • MAY. 2018 - JULY 2018

Assisted with website design, networking, security, and technical projects including podcasts, livestreams, and installment of various equipment. Demonstrated time management, communication, and professionalism.

#### MATH CENTER • CATAWBA COLLEGE • JAN. 2016 - DEC. 2018

Managed a center of learning with a group of co-workers. Skills such as, logging work time, organization, social skills, leadership, and problem solving were improved and refined.





